不是
No.
我跟他在汉堡履行过结婚手续
I went through a marriage ceremony with him
但是我之前已经有一个丈夫了
but I already had a husband.
-他还活着  -克莉丝汀这不是真的
-He's still alive. -Christine that's not true!
法官大人  我们有证据证明  证人和犯人之间的婚姻
There is proof of a marriage between the witness and the prisoner
请问那桩所谓的"之前的"
but is there any proof of a so-called
婚姻有没有证据可以证明
previous marriage?
法官大人这桩所谓的＂之前的＂婚姻有充分的文件证明
My lord the so-called previous marriage is in fact well-documented.
赫尔姆太太
Mrs Helm is this
这是你与奥托·路德  维格·赫尔姆的结婚证吗
a certificate of marriage between yourself and Otto Ludwig Helm
注册地点是布雷斯劳  时间是1942年4月18日
the ceremony having taken place in Breslau on 18 April 1942?